<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>【ZP】Rice cultivating civilization</name>
	<author>Tosenbo</author>
	<targetVersion>0.17.1546</targetVersion>
	<description>

Languages　日本語、English(Machine translation unfinished)

==================================================================

Zipangu Mod　第1弾　Rice cultivating civilization

このModは以下の要素を追加します。
①稲作と生産工程を追加する。
②製造過程中に出た副産物を使って様々なものを作成
③米俵を売る事で特産品として金儲けできる。
④テスト段階：調味料追加で調理をリアル志向にする。

リアルを追求した米の生産Modです。序盤は作業量が多いので人手が不足します。
安定すれば豊穣の恵みによって大量の収穫物を得ることができます。
！！時間と労力がかかるぶん色々な事ができるModです！！

俺達が初めて作成したModなので追加変更削除の可能性があるので十分注意してください。

匿名希望で意見・要望・感想がある方は、したらば RimWorld　MOD制作板 米スレにお願いします。
面白いネタやリアル志向な意見があった場合は随時取り込む予定です。

==================================================================

Machine translation. Sorry if it is difficult to read.

English translation is undecided as Mod production is given priority.

Zipangu Mod　Vol.1　Rice cultivating civilization

This Mod adds the following elements.
① Add rice crop and production process.
② Make various things using by-products generated during the manufacturing process.
③ Make money as special products by selling  straw rice bags.
④ Test stage: Make cooking realistic by adding seasoning.

It is Mod which added real production process of rice.
Because there is a lot of workload, there is a possibility that someone's hand is short.
If the colony is stable, you can get a large amount of crops.
！！This Mod uses a lot of time and effort.However, there are enough rewards for that.！！

For the first time is a Mod that you created.
Please be aware that there is a possibility of addition, change or deletion.

Please help me with the translation correction because English is not good.
Modification of the translation will be reflected within a few days if it is provided in XML or Folder.

==================================================================

大型Modを追加する場合
When adding another Mod

　Mod order list

　　Medieval Times
　　Vegetable Garden
　　【ZP】Rice cultivating civilization

==================================================================

プログラム担当⇒Tosenbo
テクスチャ担当⇒Wasabi99

このMODは再配布を禁止します。
This mod prohibits redistribution.

</description>
</ModMetaData>
